I live in New York and I love public
transportation, right? For all the
penises I've seen, I still love it.
You know why? Because I'm a really
insecure person. Like especially about
like the way I look and how I'm doing in
life at this point. So then I ride the
bus and I feel better.
Do that. Do that. If you're ever having
a bad day, find a bus and ride it.
cuz you'll get on there and you'll look
around and be like
I'm doing all right.
Yeah.
No, the subway helps me so much with my
insecurities. So much. It's wild. I sat
down on the subway one time next to this
hidic man.
And before I continue on with this
story, I just want to let you all know
that I am Jewish.
So, everything I'm about to say is fine.
Okay.
Another thing you should know is I'm
from Kentucky. And in Kentucky, we don't
have acidic juice. That's not a thing.
We It's the curly Q juice, by the way. I
don't know if you guys know. We don't
have them. So, when I moved to New York
and I saw them, I got all excited and I
called my friends back home in Kentucky
and I was like, "You guys, they have
extreme Jews here.
But what my friends were picturing was
not a hetic Jew. My friends were
picturing just like a guy going
skydiving while wearing a yarmaka.
They're picturing a guy who's like
extreme Jew.
You know, a guy who's like, I actually
don't need a parachute. I have a talite.
So an important rule to know for hetic
Jews is they have it's this thing called
shr ngia and it means that they're not
allowed to touch members of the opposite
sex if they're not related or married.
So,
I sat down on the subway next to this
acidic man and as I sat down, the train
rocked and then I accidentally
brushed up against him and then he
intentionally
recoiled
away.
He got as far away as he possibly could
and started praying under his breath in
Hebrew.
That's the sexiest I've ever felt.
Hands down. Hands down. I was like, "Oh,
I'm going to violate a man's religion
today."
Still got it. You know,
one of the things I missed the most, I
couldn't find a good bacon, egg, and
cheese sandwich when I moved here. I
would go to the deli and I'd be like,
"Can I get a bacon, egg, and cheese?"
And they'd be like, "I don't you know, I
don't know."
And I said, "I said all the I said it. I
said all the stuff. Just do what I said.
They have their own version. It's it's
fancier. They have like they call it a
breakfast sandwich and it normally has
some type of a garnish on it." And um an
aioli. Are you famili familiar with
aioli? It's like rich guy mayonnaise.
And I didn't know I ordered a breakfast
sandwich the first time I bit into it. I
just got a mouthful of aoli and I was
like, you got to warn you got to warn
us.
I've never had more empathy for women
than than that.
It's like you got to say something. Is
that what it's like? I don't want your
unannounced rich guy mayonnaise in my
mouth.
I miss sarcasm. I feel like people on
the East Coast are a lot more sarcastic
than they are around here. You guys have
a good sense of humor, but it's not the
same. Um, I get little I look for it in
people. I remember when we were moving
out of our last apartment into our new
apartment, my wife uh goes to the
movers, which are just three giant
Russian guys. She goes, "We need to be
out of this place and into our new place
in 3 hours. Could we do that? What do
you think about that? That's how much
money we have.
[Music]
And one of the Russian guys goes to the
other Russian guy. He goes, "Three
hours.
Maybe if magic happens."
And I was like, "Dude, that is good."
I love knowing that that guy has like
maybe like six phrases
in his back pocket to survive in a new
country and one of them is
maybe if a magic were to happen.
I love that. Anybody have anything else
they miss? Do you miss anything? Do you
live here now or you just visiting?
>> No, I live here.
>> You live here? Do you miss anything
specific from New York? Puerto Rican
people.
>> Jamaican people.
>> Dominican people. Yeah. He's like, "No,
no, no. Not Jamaican."
You could find If you look, you could
find them.
I miss um I miss having straight
friends.
You guys ever do those? You ever have
those?
I miss it, dude. All my my gay friends
vastly outnumber my uh my straight
friends. I don't know when that
happened, but the ratio is off.
And uh they took me to the parade. They
took me gay guy parade
and it was fine. I had a cool fine time.
Not a lot of notes coming from me. I do
think I didn't super need to be there
if I'm being honest. I think there were
too many straits at the gay parade. I
don't think we need to go to everything.
Not that allies are important. I think I
think a gay guy needs a straight ally.
Like a band needs a bass player.
I think it's good. You're doing a good
job. You're being support, but you turn
it down and you go over there
and you don't dress up like the lead
singer and dance around. That's the lead
singer's thing. When the bass player
starts dressing like the lead singer,
you're like, "Okay, Jeff, [__]
take it easy."
And I'm not gay, but I I was called gay
every day in high school, so I did
celebrate.
I still get called gay sometimes. I got
called gay recently for having a bedet.
Do we think having a bet is gay?
>> No.
Thank you.
Jury's still out.
Dude, if having a bedet is gay, I'm the
gayest guy.
That's my favorite place I've ever sat
down.
The pressure on that [__] is It's
alarming, too. I took the governor off.
The pressure is I'm like Iron Man. I
come up a little bit.
That's how I get food out of my back
teeth late at night.
Wonder he is.
I love that. Thank you. I have a travel
bedet now. That's how gay I am. Did you
even know they made those, dude? They
they recharge USBC.
It's beautiful. German engineering
probably if I'm guessing. I'm just
guessing. But it's great. That's the
same technology as your phone player.
Sometimes it goes off in my bag when I'm
going through TSA.
And I got to be like, it's not weird.
It's for my ass.
>> It's cool being a celebrity. I hang out
with other celebrities.
Um, one time I was right here in this
comedy club, but this woman came up to
me. I swear this is real life. She goes,
"Hey Taylor, that's so cool. You're on
America's Got Talent." I was also on a
reality show. And I was like, "Oh,
that's interesting. Uh, what show are
you on?" And she goes, "Hoarders.
[Laughter]
I don't know if you're familiar with the
TV program Hoarders,
but it's a show about filthy, disgusting
people.
Would you prefer mention to you that
they were hoarders before you shake
their hands
with your hands?
I'll be honest though, as disgusted as I
was, I was also impressed equally.
Do you know how disgusting you have to
be to be invited to be on Hoarders?
Like it's not like you know remember the
end of Double Dare when it's like if you
want to be on Double Dare send a
self-ress stamped envelope to
they don't provide this on hoarders.
They find you. Okay?
They hear about you. They smell about
you. They find you.
This woman was probably sitting in her
house one day. Then she heard her phone
ring. She heard like the muffled phone
ring noise, you know.
And then she went to where her phone
usually is. And then her eight cats were
on the phone.
They were like on the phone like meow
meow meow. How are you? I'm a cat on a
telephone.
That's not what I meant. That's funny
though. That's not what I meant. I got
it. I was show and her a cut. They're
all on the phone, you know. She's like,
"Come on, guys. Get off the phone. We
got two rings left. Come on. Come on.
Why aren't you moving?" And she's like,
"Oh, yeah. They died 3 years ago. I
forgot. I'm gross and weird." You know,
disgusting and weird, you know. So then
she scooped off all her dead cats.
And she was like, "Hello."
And the guy's like, "Hi, this is Josh,
the producer of Hoarders, the show where
we take filthy, disgusting people and we
showcase them for the whole world to see
how filthy and disgusting they are. Is
Barbara available?"
And she's like, "Speaking?"
And he's like, "Barbara, I'm so glad we
connected. I've been trying to call you
for 6 months. You never answered the
phone." And she's like, "I'm so sorry.
I'm so embarrassed. I have my dead cats.
They were on the phone.
They were like on the phone like me. I'm
a ghost cat. I'm in heaven. We go to
heaven, too. Such as dogs. I'm a cat on
the phone. It's dead. I'm a ghost cat.
But don't worry. Don't worry. Um,
they're in the trash now. It's not going
to be a problem.
And he's like, "No, no, no. Put them
back. We'll use it for the show. We love
it." This is great. I'm so glad we
connected. I understand you've been
collecting your toenails since 1972
and you categorizing them by color. This
man is so happy. We'd love to have you
star on the next episode of Hoarders.
Here's how the contract works. It'll air
for the next hundred years.
You'll be paid $0.
Everyone you know and love will disown
you.
And she's like, "Go on."
You get the joke. You get the joke.
Okay.
that joke.
>> Dude, I love basketball. Basketball is
my favorite sport. I really do love the
way they dribble up and down the court.
Uh, it's been my favorite thing as far
back as I can remember. Like, I don't
think that's normal to love the same
thing from 4 years old to 40. That's
crazy. Uninterrupted. And I've loved
basketball the same way my entire life
where I'm I'm obsessive. I'm always
trying to like memorize statistics. So,
I'm always trying to find like who is
going to become the next big superstar
in the NBA, right? And I just turned 40
and I did an audit of my Instagram
account recently.
I follow like 300
teenage boys
like, you know, like muscular, athletic,
desperate teenage boys. That can't be
good.
Yeah, man. I'm a fan of the obviously
I'm a fan of the Minnesota Timberwolves,
which
>> Yeah. I mean, I know you guys get it,
but in most places when I tell people
I'm a fan of the Timberwolves, it's like
telling someone I'm a cutter.
You know what I'm saying? They're like,
"What? Are you okay?" And it's like,
"Not really." No.
Does it hurt? Yeah, it hurts a lot. But
I get off on it.
They've been bad my whole life, but this
year they're very good and it's very
exciting. And a lot of that is uh due to
this guy on the Timberwolves, this this
guy named Anthony Edwards. He's so good
at basketball. He's such a muscular boy
and
I love him. I love him.
I was visiting my parents recently and I
was telling my mom about the
Timberwolves and I was telling her about
Anthony Edwards, how much I loved him
and and I I got kind of carried away cuz
at one point I was like, "Mom, I for
real I would jump in front of a bullet
to save his life. That's how good he is
at basketball." My mom was like, "What?"
My mom's never heard me talk about
anyone this way. And I could tell she
was a little jealous cuz she went, "What
about me?"
And I was like, "What about you?"
She's like, "Would you jump in front of
a bullet to save my life?" And then I'd
be like, "Yes, mother. I'd jump in front
of a bullet to save your life."
She didn't love my my level of sarcasm.
Uh cuz she followed that with a a truly
insane hypothetical, right? My my mom
went, "Okay, Joe, let's say I was
standing on the street next to Anthony
Edwards." And I was like, "Mom, that's
the coolest thing you've ever done."
And she's like, "Okay." And let's say
someone shot a gun in our direction and
you could jump in front of the bullet to
save one of our lives. Who you going to
save? Me or this Anthony Edwards?
And I looked at her. I was like, "Mom,
you know that's unfair. That's so
manipulative. You're my mother. I love
you. You brought me into this world.
You You've lived a long life. You know,
I don't
know what to tell you. What? You want me
to to save you and let this beautiful
boy die with his whole life ahead of
him? Absolutely not.
It's like, Mom, you did it. You raised
two kids. You were a federal judge. You
retired. None of those things has gotten
me any closer to winning an NBA
championship. Like, like, sorry.
It's like, mom, you have no jump shot.
Your handles are trash. Like, if my mom
tried to play defense in the NBA, she'd
get [__] cooked. like her ankles
would break. She has osteoporosis.
That's part of it.
Like kind of a classic upbringing. My uh
my mom stayed at home. My dad worked. My
mom way too nice. I could get away with
anything. Dad, he could get like too
intense. You know, I always say if it
was just me and my mom growing up, uh I
would be in jail right now. And if it
was just me and my father, he would be
in jail
and I would be in a wheelchair.
No, I know. I mean, some of you I know
you had a dad like that. Like, he never
crossed the line, but he got pretty
close. He got pretty close. Like,
there's a handful of times I set my dad
off. I just make him so mad. He'd just
scream out the first punishment that
came to the top of his head, storm off.
About 20 minutes later, he'd walk back
out. All right, your mother and I
disgust him.
We determined you actually do not have
to carry me on your back to my job every
day.
As previously shouted,
they were a great happy meeting, the two
of them, and I got my humor from them.
They they were always messing with each
other, poking fun at us. It was a great
atmosphere. And my mom, she was the easy
target. My poor mother, just this uh
last Thanksgiving, she always makes the
turkey. I was giving her a hard time.
I'm really laying into her. I'm like,
"Mom, you overdo the turkey." I got to
be honest. We have tools now. We can
check when it's perfectly cooked. Take
it out. Uh cuz I don't know about y'all,
Utah. I grew up in a household where
they were like, "We're pretty sure the
meat's done.
Let's cook it another 4 hours."
I grew up dunking my chicken in water
just trying to get I look like Joey
Chestnut on the 4th of July. Oh yeah.
It's like past the A1. Like you don't
need the flavor, I need the lubricant.
Like
we love to roast each other. I was
roasting my mom, but you know my mom,
the thing about her, she'll roast you
right back. And she's visiting my house
soon. And it's very scary when your
boomer mom comes to visit your
situation. They always have thoughts.
They do,
don't they?
[Applause]
My mom is coming to town.
She's going to judge me up and down. But
don't misunderstand.
She won't lecture me. She's going to do
it passive aggressively
with just a look.
Disappointing
love.
Reminds me of my childhood. Got to get
it back real good.
So I changed your password on Facebook.
Thank you.
[Applause]
She's like, "You know what, Trey? I'm
just doing what my mom taught me to do,
the cooking the turkey, whatever. I
didn't grow up with all these phones,
this and that. All I know is what my mom
taught me. And it kind of occurred to me
when we were eight months pregnant, we
got thrown a million links, podcasts,
YouTube videos, you name it, to prepare
us. And it's kind of amazing any of our
parents did as well as they did raising
us, considering they apparently just
winged it.
I think my parents philosophy was just
like, uh, let's coaches little league
teams and hit them.
the thing.
But no, I know my dad loved me. You
know, I I think a lot of my generation,
we like to blame our dads for their
problems. Blame your dad. You know, my f
my father didn't convey to me he loved
me enough. So, I have nervous poops to
this day.
It's like, well, did did your father
ever show you he loved you with his
actions? It's like, well, he worked
every day for 45 years with no sick
days, but
I never got a poem.
Maybe he loved you, right?
And I know my father loved me, but he
was old school, right? He did, you know,
wipe some dirt on a kid, real men, don't
cry, be tough, be a man, all that good
stuff. But as the years have gone on, my
father, he's gotten more and more
sensitive, very emotional. Feel like
that happens with age. Now, every time I
see my father, I leave him. I'm like,
"All right, bye bye. I love you. I'll
talk to you later." He's like, "All
right. I love you so much."
Oh, I hope you know how proud I am of
you. I was like, "Well, it's too late
now. It's too
You used to whoop me for crying, so I'm
a little confused. I'm a little
Happens with age, right? My grandma. Oh,
my grandmother. She She would she would
give me the biggest bear hug, sloppy
kiss on the cheek. And I swear I swear
after year her kisses were inching
closer and closer
until I'm pretty sure one year our
tongues touched a little bit
and teenage Trey thought he impregnated
his gam.
That's what you taught me.
I remember kids on the basketball team
and be like, "You ever done it before?"
I was like, "Yeah, with my Grammy, I
think,
God rest her soul." She left us in 2020.
2020 she passed. Not of CO. I feel like
you have to say that. Don't worry. She
did not believe in it. She did not.
I'm woke.
I know all our righteous acts are filthy
rags, but I'm woke. You know, I
understand that women got tough with the
whole beauty standards thing. All these
weird shifting beauty standards that men
are always applying. Thigh gap. Remember
that?
Remember that nonsense? If you don't
remember thigh gap, there's this thing
going around a few years back. It was
this idea that in order to be considered
at the top level of beauty, a woman when
her feet were together, there had to be
like space between her thighs or
something. Cuz I guess like no matter
how attractive a woman can be, you'd
rather see like what's on the other side
of her.
[Applause]
>> You'd rather see like half a mailbox or
something like
hubba hubba, you know?
Who came up with that? That's insane.
Like some lunatic just woke up some
morning like, "God, we need a fourth
hole. I don't care."
Put it above their knees. I'm insane.
Thigh gap is crazy. What you're saying
with thigh gap is that you want less
woman whenever possible, which like like
I guess that's the ideal woman for a man
is less woman, you know? Men whenever
possible. We want like a woman who's
like, you know, 2'6,
weighs 30 lb, has translucent skin like
a bat.
[Music]
I told you I was woke.
No one ever believes me.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Beauty standards, though.
It's much tougher for a woman obviously,
you know, woman got all these hoops they
got to jump through, you know, to
attract a man. If a woman wants to
attract a man, she's got to get in shape
and have her hair done, her nails done,
her makeup tasteful, you know, she's got
to be confident but not too bold, and
she's got to be demure, but not too not
too shy. She's got to jump through all
these hoops to attract a man. But if a
man wants to attract a woman, it's much
easier. If a man wants to attract a
woman, all he's got to do is kill Ronald
Reagan.
[Laughter]
The joke there is back when John
Hinckley took a took a took a try at
Ronald Reagan, he was doing so in order
so that would Jodie Foster would fall in
love with him.
That's right. I've entered the fun facts
[Music]
portion of my set.
Django
suffers from night terrors.
You all get those, right? Night terrors.
You wake up in the middle of the night
paralyzed
with a guy in the corner of the room.
Midnight man.
I hate that guy, man.
I hate the midnight man.
>> Like, like, what does this gesture even
mean?
[Applause]
Use your words, Midnight Man.
I don't care that you don't have a
mouth.
[Laughter]
I think I'm getting a little off track
here.
What was I talking about? Men and women
are different, right?
No, I was talking about beauty
standards, men, women, sexuality, the
whole thing. You know, sexuality
obviously is a big topic of discussion
these days. You know, everyone's always
jawing about it. And I, you know, I'm
I'm a modern, sensible person. I believe
that sexuality is a spectrum. It ranges
from uh people who are going to heaven
[Music]
triggered much less.
You're triggered.
Don't pretend like you're not triggered.
I said something mean and now you're
unhappy about it. Checkmate.
[Laughter]
No, sexuality though, that's the topic
of the next joke.
I consider myself heterosexual with
maybe a caveat here and there, you know,
like though I consider myself straight,
I do enjoy Greek art.
[Music]
I'll go to a museum and see like an
ancient vase that features three nude
Greek boys chasing each other around a
mulberry bush
and I'll be like, "Huh?"
[Music]
Now, this speaks to me.
If only life could imitate art, you
know?
It's wild how the ancient Greeks
invented both democracy and child
molestation.
[Laughter]
What an ambitious one-two punch.
How could that possibly have even been
received? Like, wow, ancient Greeks, you
they probably called them regular Greeks
back then.
Wow. Regular Greeks,
you guys have invented representative
democracy. Greece is now the cradle of
civilization. What do you got next?
>> Cradle, huh?
>> To the bathous.
[Music]
>> I don't know if Oliver have kids.
I see the appeal though, right? Have a
kid, have a little version of yourself.
Teach him to fear what you fear.
I don't know. I don't know if I have
what it takes to be a dad. I think maybe
at best I could be like an emotionally
abusive stepfather.
Why not? I like Coors Light.
I can see myself posting up on the
couch. Where you going with them books,
boy?
You going to the library?
You going to the library to get more
books?
We never had no books in Kuwait, that's
for sure.
[Laughter]
I feel like I've been doing a lot of
glaring tonight.
[Laughter]
I realize that I can make people
uncomfortable occasionally, you know,
and that can be, you know, one-on-one
conversation or even when I'm just
following them out to their car.
I am getting older though. There's no
way around that. It happens suddenly,
right? Getting older. One day you wake
up, you're old, you have a favorite kind
of cracker.
You got to fill out a form online and to
find your birth year, you got to do that
big Price's right spin to get down
there.
Two fingers on the trackpad like
Jeez, man. Not even the Leman Brothers
bankruptcy yet.
Getting older.
My attention span is shortening by the
day. Especially when you compare it to
what it was when I was a child. Cuz like
when I was a kid, like I would just read
books all day long. That's all I would
do day in and day out. We had this big
chair in our living room and I would
just sit there and read books. You know,
I was super cute.
I read books all day long. I love
reading, you know. I love reading
stories about hobbits and box car
children.
[Music]
I used to love those little hobos.
But I'd read all day. You know, I'd wake
up and I'd get to the big chair and I'd
read the same book for like 5 hours
straight. Then I'd sprint to the kitchen
and eat lunch as quickly as I could so I
could get back to the big chair and read
the same book for like seven more hours.
It's crazy cuz when you compare it
against who I am now, it's like this
deranged lunatic
where every morning I just wake up like,
"God, my phone.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, thank god it's in my hands again.
Okay.
Okay. Funny video. Funny video. Yeah,
that's funny. That's funny.
The premise is taking too long to
establish. Next video. Next video. Sad
video.
Yeah, this will make me happy. Okay. Sad
video. Yeah. The soldier is getting back
from one of the countries
and his dogs there to greet him. I knew
it would always work out. I need to buy
something.
I need to get something that'll make me
happy. All the other things I bought
didn't make me happy. This this
hamburger gloves. I need the hamburger
gloves. If I buy the hamburger gloves,
that will be it. I'll be happy. All the
other things didn't make me happy, but
the hamburger gloves. Well, I need a
company of a woman. I need companionship
of a woman on a dating website. Let's
look at all the women on the Oh, no.
This is weird. Next woman. Next woman. I
don't like that woman. I need a better
woman.
She's using too many exclamation points.
No, I don't. I don't. That's not what I
want. What I want is what I want is I
don't remember what I want. What do I
want? I remember what I want. What I
wanted. Would I help me, please? I don't
want to. Help me. Help me. Help. Help.
Help. Help. And at this point, it's like
8:15 a.m.
disgraceful
kind of makes me wonder what happened to
the uh little boy in the big chair,
right?
I hope he's doing okay,
wherever he is. 25 is a great age, by
the way. It's a good age. I got a
brother. He's 28. It's pretty cool. Big
difference though between the younger
people and me is that I was bullied
relentlessly. Uh my brother did not
experience this fate. I say bullied. It
was more just like lowkey sexual
assault.
It was a lot of like wrapping your dick
around your wrist and asking a slow kid
what time it is.
He can't read a regular clock.
Don't hit him with a dick clock.
Another cool one was you'd take your
ball bag, put it on top of your buddy's
hat. You know, I like I like I like your
yarmaka, you know. That was
that was a good one. Uh the worst one
for sure was this game called Warm Up My
Face.
You sound like you played that game.
That's the laugh of a victim.
I would ask you if you ever played, but
I don't want you to have a seizure, sir.
So,
I don't want your [__] brain to pop.
You're right to leave. I understand.
Yeah. Warm up. My face went like this.
There was a bigger boy named Wyatt Maze,
and he would come up to me in school and
he'd be like, "Sam, your face looks
pretty cold." I would say, "Who [__]
told you that?
My face is an adequate temperature,
Wyatt?" And he would say, "I don't know,
man. Looks pretty cold to me." And I
would say, "I will swear on any book you
call holy.
It is warm, Wyatt." And as I was begging
and pleading, another kid named Anthony
would kneel behind me, and Wyatt would
shove me over him. As I was laying on my
back, Wyatt would pull his pants down
and sit on my face.
Oh, yeah. He was quite cunning, this
Wyatt.
He was an improviser.
And then he would say, "I bet your face
is warm now." And I would say,
cuz I was wearing a boy as a mask.
So, I suffered that. All right. But the
young people, you guys had to deal with
a whole different American calamity,
which is the uh the deeply American
problem of the school shooting. You had
to live in fear of that. Just [__] go
with me.
Chill. All right.
I was bullied. you had to live in fear
of the school shootings. Uh, you know, a
big difference. I will say this though,
school shootings are a pretty effective
means of bullying.
It's pretty efficient. Really, Wyatt
only had one butt.
Imagine if he had a gun that shot 15
butts a second.
He could have warmed up a lot of faces.
See, it's a butt joke, everyone.
Don't worry, it's okay.
Uh, I never envied you guys. One time I
envied your situation
>> cuz in sixth grade, uh, I was on a field
trip to the Denver Art Museum and I was
in the gifted and talented program. So,
I had to give a speech on a Picasso
painting
>> and I had to like explain what the stars
represented. And as I was up there
boring my entire class, another kid
came, Jesse, came up behind me and
pulled down my basketball shorts.
And I was 5'10", you know, [__] 220
lb, 11 years old.
So it was adult body, baby penis.
And this was pre 911, so
there was no cloud cover. It was
just full pig snout right there.
As I was standing up there exposed to my
entire class, I would have much rather
been shot in the [__] head.
That would have been a mercy killing
cuz now I'm labeled, you know, adult
body penis. That's all I am forever. I'm
baby penis Sam. And even like if I'm
shot later in a school shooting, they're
not going to remember me as friend to
all Sam talent. They're going to be
like, "Oh, did you hear about Sam?" No.
What happened? Oh, he shot in that
school shooting. Oh,
wait. Baby dick Sam.
Oh, that's It's too bad.
Where was Where was he shot?
Definitely not the dick.
The shooter didn't have a scope on that
thing. He wasn't a sniper. So, yes,
that's a difficult joke to tell. But
hey, I'm from Colorado. We kind of
invented it. So, it's okay. All right.
Any parents here who had to work really
hard to make a baby?
There you go. God bless you. It takes a
lot of trying. It took me and my wife
two years of trying to make our baby.
Two years of trying. That's the term
people use for coming in your wife.
People are real comfortable with it. My
mom would be like, "Are you guys
trying?"
Mom, are you asking if I'm blasting
loads inside of Ashley? Is that what
you're asking?
Is that what you're asking comfortably
at the dinner table?
Are you guys trying? Huh? Getting it in
there.
No butt stuff. I want grandkids.
My mom is obsessed with grandkids, dude.
One time me and my wife were staying at
my parents house and my wife was
ovulating cuz she's a little [__] And
sorry, I don't believe in science. Um,
and my mom found out and she goes, "Hey,
if you guys have to try, why don't you
use our room?"
She said, "The bed's more comfortable up
there."
She's like, "It'll be quieter." I'm
like, "It won't be quieter up here
though while we're doing it."
But it took us 2 years because my wife
is 38. So, she technically had a
geriatric pregnancy. Do you know that's
the offensive term they give to a
middle-aged woman getting pregnant? As
if at 35, your vagina gets a little
walker with tennis balls on it. Like, a
middle-aged woman opens her legs and all
you see is a coupon for soup.
But it's true. It takes longer when
you're older. You know, if you ever see
a teenage girl who's pregnant, tip your
hat. That's the smartest girl in the
class. She ran the numbers. I'm not
kidding. If you have a teenage daughter,
tell her to get knocked up now.
IVF is expensive and she can take math
at any point in the rest of her life.
Cuz it's hard to get a woman pregnant
when you're trying to do it. When you're
not trying, pretty easy.
You could sneeze on a woman at
Coachella. She's like, "Fuck twins."
But when you are trying, it's tough. You
got to wait for a harvest moon.
Pluck one feather off a goose, tickler
cooch for three or four minutes
while singing a John Mayer tune.
Cuz here's what I didn't know about
women's bodies. They're magical. They
make babies, but they only do it two or
three days a month. Ovaries only work
two or three days a month. Ovaries are
like government workers.
They're always there, but they're never
doing [__] for anybody. Meanwhile,
balls, it's not complex labor, but
they're showing up every godamn day
like illegal workers.
[Applause]
Ready for hard labor. Unless you've been
drinking, then it's less hard and more
labor.
No, but really, I know we're close to
Mexico, but balls really are the illegal
immigrant of the body, aren't they?
Think about the dick gets all the
credit. The balls are in the background
putting in the real hours,
sharing that little apartment.
[Applause]
And everybody thinks they smell. So, I'm
sorry. I had to do three.
I had to do three.
So, you get those three or four days and
you got to [__] like crazy in that
window, right? And I'm 40. I like to
[__] twice a week. There's a lot on
Netflix.
I'm sorry. I don't care how good your
[__] is. It's not better than Squid
Game. No way. You know what I mean?
But you get those three or four days,
two or three days, you got to [__]
constantly. I had to come six times in 3
days. Six times. That dude's super
excited about all that coming. Six times
is too much for a man my age. The last
time one sperm came out,
it was one little hillbilly trucker hat
wearing sperm.
Just like, what's up?
Everybody else went home.
Still trying to meet that egg.
And me and my wife, we were like, we
want a baby. We want a baby, but we just
we don't want to [__] each other.
So, I was like, we got to find something
to do. So, we started watching porn
during our baby making attempts. And
that's a weird thing to do with your
partner cuz you learn what each other
are into. And sometimes you're like, I
don't think you should be a parent.
Turns out my wife is some dark dark
derogatory misogynistic porn. Like she's
a feminist, but not when it comes to
porn.
She likes see I mean she cried when Ruth
Bader Ginsburg died. She likes seeing a
woman take a load to the face of
multiple ankles.
She's Hillary Clinton in the streets and
a big old Bill Clinton in the sheets.
You understand what I'm saying?
And I'm pretty generic with porn. You
guys, you know, sir, right? You know me
in porn,
right, Todd? You know all about it,
right?
I'm pretty generic with porn. I like two
straight women pretending to be gay.
Right. A couple of American straight
lesbians. Not my wife. No. She likes
that evil porn that's always up in the
side of the red tube or the up porn or
wherever the [__] you jerk off to. You
know those evil videos of one woman and
nine naked men standing around her. And
you're like, "Who's that for?" Turns out
it's for the mother of my daughter.
That's who that's for.
And she names each guy like they're in a
little boy band.
And I thought we were going to have a
male child. I thought we were going to
have a boy. I have a lot of back hair. I
watch the UFC. I thought we were going
to have a boy, you know. So, we would
jerk on. I mean, no, we would jerk on.
Sorry. I was thinking about what I would
do after the show. Um,
no, but I thought we'd have a boy. I
did. I thought we'd have a boy. So, we
would watch porn to make the baby. I
would always secretly save the link cuz
I figured one day I could give my son
the link.
And when he turns 15, he can jerk off to
the scene that made him.
And I think that's what the kids call an
NFT.
No, it took us two years. It took us 2
years of trying to make this baby. And
eventually my wife told me I had to
check my semen, which was scary cuz I
have never checked my semen before. I
have checked myself for semen.
But I never checked my semen, you know,
and I'm like, "Dude, I don't know what's
in my semen. What if it turns out I'm
gay?" You know what I mean? Like, I
don't know how this works. Like, if
they're going to look at my semen, I
want it to be phenomenal. You know, I
want the doctor to hold it up to the
light and be like,
[Laughter]
"This is one guy.
That's one guy.
>> You sure that's not all four Ninja
Turtles? That's one guy.
Gets on the intercom. Everybody get in
here. You got to see this.
You got to taste this.
I was like, I don't know if I want to
check my semen. My wife goes, I make the
money. You're going to check your dick?
Yes, ma'am. I will do that right now.
So, so we go to the fertility doctor.
Went to the fertility doctor and he told
us, he goes, Mo, you got to give us a
sample. you can do it here or you can do
it at home. And I was like, how would I
do it here? And he said, well, we have
an iPad. And then he just lifted up an
iPad in a Ziploc plastic bag. Just a
little Ziploc plastic jerkoff slave
iPads just staring out at me like, "No,
I don't want to do it again."
Like all day long, this little camera
stares up at 40-year-old men like, "Why
did I wait?"
He's like, "Yeah, we got an iPad. I use
it at lunch sometimes.
I got it bookmarked
and my wife's a doctor, like I said, so
she's like, "Just jerk off in the cup.
I'll bring it into the hospital where I
work." But I'm like, "Yeah, but that
just seems like a [__] move to be like,
you take it.
You already make the money. Now
transport my broken jizz."
Like, no, I'm a man. I drive my own cup
of J to the hospital while listening to
Metallica.
But here's the thing, and I don't want
to gross you out, but this is true. On
the cup, when you do this, it says you
got to get it to the hospital in 1 hour.
You have to get it to the hospital in 1
hour. And it says you have to hold it to
your body to keep it warm. So, you got
to jerk off and then immediately cuddle
your 6 million unborn ghost children.
And I don't know how you guys jerk off.
I do it butt naked. That's just how I do
it. Where my butt naked jerkers at?
>> [__] yeah. I don't like sitting there
with my pants down. I feel like I'm
trying to get away with something. I
feel like I snuck into my neighbor's
house and I'm stealing Wi-Fi. the
oldfashioned way.
So I had to jerk off the cup, get
dressed, fight LA traffic, you know, and
[__] I stopped at Starbucks. That was a
mistake. They're like, "Is that a gun?"
I'm like, "It's J." Like, "That's
worse."
I'm like, "Oh, this jizz is for a kid."
I race into the hospital. There's a big
line to drop off the sample. It's like
24, you know, the time is we're out of
time. It's Mission Impossible. There's a
big line, you know, but it said, "If
your sample has an expiration, you can
cut the line." Now, I've lived in LA for
years. I've lived in LA for years. I can
never get in anywhere. Felt good to cut
the line.
Felt like I knew the DJ. I was like,
"Yep, I'm here with Jiz. What's up,
dog?"
So, I get up and I got to hand my cup of
J to a nurse, a woman who knows I jerked
off maximum 58 minutes ago.
So, she's looking at me like, "Well,
he's pretty sweaty. He might have done
that in the elevator."
And she had no tact. I was like, "Uh, my
sample has an expiration." And she goes,
"Semen?
Is it seaman?"
And an old man's like, "Why does he get
the cut?" She's like, "Seaman, sir.
Low grade."
So they tested it, right? And guys, we
always hear we have swimmers, but we
assume, well, we got Michael Phelps,
right? That's what I got. A little sack
of Michael Phelps lover swimmers, right?
That's what you got. Michael Phelps
swimmers. We just assume that's what I
got. Little Michael Phelps swimmers. Not
necessarily. He might also have that fat
kid at summer camp who swam in his
t-shirt cuz he's got little [__] tits
that would float in the water.
I think Travis was his name.
That could be your swimmers. Cuz the
doctor said to me, he goes, "Mo, you
have good you have good semen, but you
have bad semen mobility."
So I was like, "So my dick's like a
parade float full of fat guys with bad
ankles?" Like that's pretty much
first of all I don't even know like bad
semen mobility like how mobile does
seaman have to be? I put it in my wife's
body. I'm not putting on her back like
good luck fellas.
You got a Lord of the Rings quest ahead
of you.
So I was all bummed out, you know. I was
all bummed out. And then my wife, God
bless her, says, "I don't think you have
bad seam mobility. You should check
again." I'm like, "Well, how would you
know? What do you feel?" whipping around
on little wave runners in there.
So, I checked again. The doctor goes,
"Oh, your semen's fine." I was like,
"What happened last time?" And he said,
"Quote, sometimes balls have a bad day."
And I'm like, "Well, I'm about to shoot
a comedy special. I'm going to have to
name it that."
[Applause]
That's a lot of J talk. It's a lot of J
talk.
Lot of Thank you guys. You guys stuck in
there. You know, you stuck in there. I
think one or two people actually came
during that. That was ironic.
Conspiracy theories.
Oh, I'm into it.
But I'm not into the mainstream ones.
Like my dad, you know? He's one of those
guys that wouldn't get the get the vax,
you know? He's like, I don't want
computer chips in my blood, Luke, and
the government [__] tracking my
whereabouts, dude. I'm like, you have a
smartphone. They know where you're at.
Your location services are on. They can
find you. It's also listening to you.
You know, that's why when you go on like
Amazon, it pre-predicts that you want to
buy more wrestling t-shirts.
[Laughter]
[Music]
And when you go on Pornhub, it knows
you're into stepdaughter stuff.
What? He loves it.
He absolutely loves it.
He cannot get enough.
>> I don't know why I know that.
[Music]
Not me, though. I'm a trailblazer,
right? I like to be the first guy that
comes up with a conspiracy theory. You
know what I mean?
I think that JFK got shot by that Oswalt
guy. I think we landed on the moon in
1969.
I do not really think that there is more
than meets the eye.
No funny business there. I believe those
ones.
But I got But I got But I got But I got
a conspiracy theory for you. Here it
goes. Here it goes. Here it goes. Here
it goes. My conspiracy theory. Y'all
know those packages of wet wipes that
have the realable tops. The ones that
peel back the soft packs. You know what
I'm talking about?
I kind of think they make it hard for
you. Cuz when you go to grab one, you
always end up with two. Then you're
like, "Shit, I only needed one." But now
that they are in the open air, I guess
what's done? It's done. And then they
make it so hard to slip them things back
inside of the package neatly. I think
they do that [__] intentionally to make
us use more wipes discreetly.
[Applause]
Can I get an amen?
[__] amen.
I think it's messed up. Yeah, that big
wipe would do that to us.
[__] you, big wipe, for making us spend
tens of dollars more per year on wipes.
That ain't in my budget, dude.
Don't even get me started on those
stupid iPhone chargers. I think they
designed them cords to break after four
or five uses. I think that women's
clothing pockets are so small on
purpose. I think they're in cahoots to
make you ladies still buy purses.
>> Seriously, what you're supposed to fit
in those tiny little jeans pocket?
Serious question.
like a single M&M
but not a peanut M&M
cuz a peanut M&M
is a thick boy.
These lady jeans don't got the square
footage for the chubby little M&M.
Sometimes I think they change the name
of [__] like we ain't going to notice
it.
But you know we [__] known as him.
[Music]
When I was growing up, my dad said, "Rap
it before you tap it, Luke. You do not
want to get no genital warts, my dude.
But you don't really hear about genital
warts no more."
Odd. Did they go away?
They didn't. They're still around.
What's the most popular STD there is?
Shut it out.
>> Herpes is wrong, but it says a lot about
you.
That's a top five.
Herpes is a good guess, but it's HPV.
Yeah. A little world for HPV.
Lot of HPV fans out in the crowd.
human papilloma virus and like 90% of us
have it and it mostly kills women.
>> Sure. Yeah. Throw that on the pile of
[__] only y'all got to worry about.
Meanwhile, me and the boys out here
spreading the bug, not wearing condoms.
It definitely does not work. It feels so
much more rad when you don't have
HP
human virus. What's a pavalon? I'll save
y'all a Google. It's a [__]
genital war. We all have genital warts,
you guys. They just changed the name of
that [__] to make it sound less
disgusting, but we all have it.
So many people hating on mayo
and it's like we get it. Sarah,
you do not like mayonnaise.
Do you like aoli? Sarah.
Oh, you do. That's cool. That's rad.
Cuz it's literally mayonnaise.
You are eating mayonnaise. They put
garlic in it, but it's [__] mayo.
Quit lying to yourself, Sarah.
You're not better than us, Sarah.
What else is there? Oh, yeah. Epstein
didn't kill himself.
So much.
[Applause]
Thank you.